myweddingsongs.com 2019-12-09

# Privacy, Terms & Disclosure | My Wedding Songs

1) Privacy Notice

My Wedding Songs found at https://www.myweddingsongs.com/ (“Website”) is governed by the following privacy policy (“Privacy Policy”).

We respect your privacy and are committed to protecting it. The purpose of this Privacy Policy is to inform you what personally identifiable information we may collect and how it may be used. This statement only applies to this Website.

WHAT INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT AND HOW IS IT USED?

Information You Voluntarily Submit to the Website: We may collect personal information from you such as your name or email address. For example, you may voluntarily submit information to the Website by leaving a comment, subscribing to a newsletter, or submitting a contact form. In addition, you are able to create a user profile, which allows you to create a username and password. We will store the username, but your password will not be visible in our records.

Automatically-Collected Information: We automatically collect certain information about you and the device with which you access the Website. For example, when you use the Website, we will log your IP address, operating system type, browser type, referring website, pages you viewed, and the dates/times when you accessed the Website. We may also collect information about actions you take when using the Website, such as links clicked.

Cookies: We may log information using cookies, which are small data files stored on your browser by the Website. We may use both session cookies, which expire when you close your browser, and persistent cookies, which stay on your browser until deleted, to provide you with a more personalized experience on the Website.

HOW YOUR INFORMATION MAY BE USED

We may use the information collected in the following ways:

  * To operate and maintain the Website;
  * To create your account, identify you as a user of the Website, and customize the Website for your account; 
  * To send you promotional information, such as newsletters. Each email promotion will provide information on how to opt-out of future mailings;
  * To send you administrative communications, such as administrative emails, confirmation emails, technical notices, updates on policies, or security alerts;
  * To respond to your comments or inquiries;
  * To provide you with user support;
  * To track and measure advertising on the Website;
  * To protect, investigate, and deter against unauthorized or illegal activity.

THIRD-PARTY USE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION

We may share your information with third parties when you explicitly authorize us to share your information.

Additionally, the Website may use third-party service providers to service various aspects of the Website. Each third-party service provider’s use of your personal information is dictated by their respective privacy policies.

The Website currently uses the following third-party service providers:

Google Analytics – this service tracks Website usage and provides information such as referring websites and user actions on the Website. Google Analytics may capture your IP address, but no other personal information is captured by Google Analytics.

MailChimp – this service is used for delivery of email updates and newsletters. We store your name and email address for purposes of delivering such communications. Please refer to Mail Chimp’s privacy policy for further information.

At this time, your personal information is not shared with any other third-party applications. This list may be amended from time to time in the Website’s sole discretion.

Except when required by law, we will not sell, distribute, or reveal your email addresses or other personal information without your consent; however, we may disclose or transfer personal information collected through the Website to third parties who acquire all or a portion of our business, which may be the result of a merger, consolidation, or purchase of all or a portion of our assets, or in connection with any bankruptcy or reorganization proceeding brought by or against us.

ANONYMOUS DATA

From time to time, we may use anonymous data, which does not identify you alone, or when combined with data from other parties. This type of anonymous data may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses. Examples of this anonymous data may include analytics or information collected from cookies.

PUBLICLY VISIBLE INFORMATION

If you create a user profile on the Website or leave a comment, certain information may be publicly visible. To create a user profile, you must choose a username and password and input your email address for profile confirmation. Your email address will never be available publicly. At your option, you may also add an avatar, a profile description, and a link to your website.

You may also choose to link your Facebook, Instagram, and Google Account.

Users may see your username, avatar, profile description and website information.

COOKIES

The Website uses cookies to store visitors’ preferences, record user-specific information on what pages users access or visit, ensure that visitors are not repeatedly sent the same banner ads, customize Website content based on visitors’ browser type or other information that the visitor sends. Cookies may also be used by third-party services, such as Google Analytics, as described herein.

Users may, at any time, prevent the setting of cookies, by the Website, by using a corresponding setting of your internet browser and may thus permanently deny the setting of cookies. Furthermore, already set cookies may be deleted at any time via an Internet browser or other software programs. This is possible in all popular Internet browsers. However, if users deactivate the setting of cookies in your Internet browser, not all functions of our Website may be entirely usable.

GOOGLE AND THE DOUBLECLICK DART COOKIE

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on My Wedding Songs.  
Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to My Wedding Songs visitors based on the visitor’s visit to My Wedding Songs and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

ADVERTISING

Display Ads

We may use third-party advertising companies to serve content and advertisements when you visit the Website, which may use cookies, as noted above.

Retargeting Ads

From time to time, the Website may engage in remarketing efforts with third-party companies, such as Google, Facebook, or Instagram, in order to market the Website. These companies use cookies to serve ads based on someone’s past visits to the Website.

Affiliate Program Participation

The Website may engage in affiliate marketing, which is done by embedding tracking links into the Website. If you click on a link to an affiliate partnership, a cookie will be placed on your browser to track any sales for purposes of commissions.

My Wedding Songs is a participant in the Amazon Services LLC Associates Program, an affiliate advertising program designed to provide a means for sites to earn advertising fees by advertising and links to Amazon.com. As part of this Amazon Associates program, the Website will post customized links, provided by Amazon, to track the referrals to their website. This program utilizes cookies to track visits for the purposes of assigning commission on these sales.

Newsletters

On the Website, you may subscribe to our newsletter, which may be used for advertising purposes. All newsletters sent may contain tracking pixels. The pixel is embedded in emails and allows an analysis of the success of online marketing campaigns. Because of these tracking pixels, we may see if and when you open an email and which links within the email you click. Also, this allows the Website to adapt the content of future newsletters to the interests of the user. This behavior will not be passed on to third parties.

RIGHTS RELATED TO YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

Opt-out – You may opt-out of future email communications by following the unsubscribe links in our emails. You may also notify us at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) to be removed from our mailing list.

Access – You may access the personal information we have about you by submitting a request to [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

Amend – You may contact us at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) to amend or update your personal information.

Forget – In certain situations, you may request that we erase or forget your personal data. To do so, please submit a request to [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

Please note that we may need to retain certain information for recordkeeping purposes or to complete transactions, or when required by law.

SENSITIVE PERSONAL INFORMATION

At no time should you submit sensitive personal information to the Website. This includes your social security number, information regarding race or ethnic origin, political opinions, religious beliefs, health information, criminal background, or trade union memberships. If you elect to submit such information to us, it will be subject to this Privacy Policy.

CHILDREN’S INFORMATION

The Website does not knowingly collect any personally identifiable information from children under the age of 16. If a parent or guardian believes that the Website has personally identifiable information of a child under the age of 16 in its database, please contact us immediately at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) and we will use our best efforts to promptly remove such information from our records.

**How To Change the Information You Provided Us**  
Please send us an email to [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) or request through our contact us form.

My Wedding Songs uses third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.

2) General Disclaimer

By using My Wedding Songs, you signify your acceptance of these Terms. If you do not agree to these terms, please do not use this site. The information published on My Wedding Songs is to be used for informational purposes only. While My Wedding Songs has tried to provide accurate information, there may be inadvertent technical inaccuracies, and typographical errors, for which we apologize. My Wedding Songs expressly disclaims all liability for the use or interpretation by others of information contained in My Wedding Songs or hyper-linked sites. This site may be linked to other sites which are not maintained by My Wedding Songs. My Wedding Songs is not responsible for the content of those sites.

The terms and conditions provided on this site will be interpreted and governed pursuant to the laws of Nevada, U.S.A., notwithstanding any principles of conflicts of law. If any part of these terms and conditions is unlawful, void, or unenforceable, that part will be deemed severable and will not affect the validity and enforceability of any remaining provisions. My Wedding Songs can revise these terms and conditions at any time by updating this site. My Wedding Songs describes products and services that may not be available worldwide. We reserve the right to make changes at any time without notice. By using My Wedding Songs, you signify your acceptance of these Terms. If you do not agree to these terms, please do not use this site. This Agreement may not be modified, amended, and/or changed by you in any manner; however, you may choose to terminate your membership at your choosing.

All information and use of My Wedding Songs are provided “as is” and “as available” without warranty of any kind. My Wedding Songs makes no representations or warranties that the site will meet users’ requirements or expectations and will result in interrupted, timely, secure or fault-free basis. Your use of this site is solely at the users’ risk. My Wedding Songs is under no obligation to provide users with any technical support.

My Wedding Songs reserves the right to modify or discontinue any area of the website with or without user notice.

3) Information Published

This site is an interactive computer service which may have information posted hereon another information content provider other than My Wedding Songs, it’s employees, affiliates and users. My Wedding Songs shall not be treated as the publisher or speaker of any information provided by another information content provider pursuant to the communications decency Act. 47 U.S.C. 230. My Wedding Songs, it’s employees, affiliates and users shall not be held liable on account of A) considers to be obscene, lewd, lascivious, filthy, excessively violent, harassing, or otherwise objectionable, whether or not such material is constitutionally protected or B) any action taken to enable or make available to information content providers or others the technical means to restrict access to material

My Wedding Songs does not claim ownership of the materials provided to My Wedding Songs or posted, uploaded, inputted or submitted to the My Wedding Songs site. However, by registering, posting, uploading, inputting or submitting materials/information you are granting to My Wedding Songs permission to use your materials/information in connection with the operation of the My Wedding Songs site and its use by others including, without limitation , the rights to: publicly display, reformat, publish your name with such material/information. By posting, uploading, inputting, providing or submitting your material/information you warrant and represent that you own or otherwise control all the rights of such material/information.

4) Payments

Visitors to My Wedding Songs may subscribe or opt-in for advertising packages. Electronic payments are handled externally through Paypal. My Wedding Songs does not collect any information other than the service requested. For further information about Paypal electronic payments, please see our provider’s policy ([http://paypal.com/cgi-bin/webscr?cmd=p/gen/privacy-outside](https://paypal.com/cgi-bin/webscr?cmd=p/gen/privacy-outside)). In addition, we offer product or services by our affiliates such as iTunes and Amazon. Please refer to their own privacy statements.

5) Communication Usage

The My Wedding Songs site may contain phone numbers, website addresses, and various types of email, direct or other communication facilities designed for members to contact wedding product and service providers and for the same providers to contact My Wedding Songs members (as Communication Usage). Communication Usage also entails all Guest books. By utilizing My Wedding Songs, you agree to the Communication Usage only to inquire of listed services or products that a proper and related to the particular Communication Usage. 

By the way of example, and not limited to, you agree that when related to Communication Usage, you will not:

  * Defame, abuse, harass, stalk, threaten or otherwise violate the legal rights of privacy and publicity) of others.
  * Publish, post, upload, distribute any profane, defamatory, infringing, obscene, indecent or unlawful topic, name, material or information.
  * Send messages that contain software or other protected material by intellectual property unless you own the rights to it.Send messages or create vendor ratings that contain false or misleading information.
  * Request information/quotations for or offer to buy products or services that you do not have the intention and ability to purchase.
  * Advertise, quote, or offer to sell products or services that you do not have the ability to sell, harvest or otherwise collect information about others, including contact information such as email addresses, for the purpose of building contact lists.
  * You may not send unsolicited email to any My Wedding Songs member that has not specifically made its email available for such purpose.
  * My Wedding Songs shall have no obligation to monitor Communication Usage. However, My Wedding Songs reserves the right to review materials posted to a Communication Usage and to remove any materials in its sole discretion. My Wedding Songs reserves the right to terminate access to any or all of the Communication Usage at any time without notice.

6) Affiliate Disclosure

The Website may engage in affiliate marketing, which is done by embedding tracking links into the Website. If you click on a link to an affiliate partnership, a cookie will be placed on your browser to track any sales for purposes of commissions.

WeddingMuseum LLC, dba My Wedding Songs, is a participant in the Amazon Services LLC Associates Program, an affiliate advertising program designed to provide a means for sites to earn advertising fees by advertising and links to Amazon.com. As part of this Amazon Associates program, the Website will post customized links, provided by Amazon, to track the referrals to their website. This program utilizes cookies to track visits for the purposes of assigning commission on these sales.

7) My Wedding Songs App Privacy Policy

This privacy policy has been compiled to better serve those who are concerned with how their ‘Personally Identifiable Information’ (PII) is being used online. PII, as described in US privacy law and information security, is information that can be used on its own or with other information to identify, contact, or locate a single person, or to identify an individual in context. Please read our privacy policy carefully to get a clear understanding of how we collect, use, protect or otherwise handle your Personally Identifiable Information in accordance with our website.

What personal information do we collect from the people that visit our blog, website or app?

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name, email address or other details to help you with your experience.

When do we collect information?

We collect information from you when you subscribe to a newsletter, fill out a form or enter information on our site.

Provide us with feedback on our products or services  
How do we use your information?

We may use the information we collect from you when you register, make a purchase, sign up for our newsletter, respond to a survey or marketing communication, surf the website, or use certain other site features in the following ways:

• To personalize your experience and to allow us to deliver the type of content and product offerings in which you are most interested.  
• To improve our website in order to better serve you.  
• To allow us to better service you in responding to your customer service requests.  
• To send periodic emails regarding your order or other products and services.  
• To follow up with them after correspondence (live chat, email or phone inquiries)

How do we protect your information?

We do not use vulnerability scanning and/or scanning to PCI standards.  
We only provide articles and information. We never ask for credit card numbers.  
We use regular Malware Scanning.

Your personal information is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of persons who have special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. In addition, all sensitive/credit information you supply is encrypted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology.

We implement a variety of security measures when a user enters, submits, or accesses their information to maintain the safety of your personal information.

All transactions are processed through a gateway provider and are not stored or processed on our servers.

Do we use ‘cookies’?

Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the site’s or service provider’s systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. For instance, we use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart. They are also used to help us understand your preferences based on previous or current site activity, which enables us to provide you with improved services. We also use cookies to help us compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.

We use cookies to:  
• Compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interactions in order to offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may also use trusted third-party services that track this information on our behalf.

You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser settings. Since browser is a little different, look at your browser’s Help Menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies.

If you turn cookies off, some features will be disabled. It won’t affect the user’s experience that make your site experience more efficient and may not function properly.

However, you will still be able to place orders .

Third-party disclosure

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your Personally Identifiable Information unless we provide users with advance notice. This does not include website hosting partners and other parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or serving our users, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release information when it’s release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others’ rights, property or safety. 

However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

Third-party links

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third-party products or services on our website. These third-party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

Google

Google’s advertising requirements can be summed up by Google’s Advertising Principles. They are put in place to provide a positive experience for users. https://support.google.com/adwordspolicy/answer/1316548?hl=en 

We use Google AdSense Advertising on our website.

Google, as a third-party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on previous visits to our site and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt-out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google Ad and Content Network privacy policy.

We have implemented the following:  
• Demographics and Interests Reporting  
• DoubleClick Platform Integration

We, along with third-party vendors such as Google use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookies) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) or other third-party identifiers together to compile data regarding user interactions with ad impressions and other ad service functions as they relate to our website.

Opting out:  
Users can set preferences for how Google advertises to you using the Google Ad Settings page. Alternatively, you can opt out by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative Opt Out page or by using the Google Analytics Opt Out Browser add on.

California Online Privacy Protection Act

CalOPPA is the first state law in the nation to require commercial websites and online services to post a privacy policy. The law’s reach stretches well beyond California to require any person or company in the United States (and conceivably the world) that operates websites collecting Personally Identifiable Information from California consumers to post a conspicuous privacy policy on its website stating exactly the information being collected and those individuals or companies with whom it is being shared. – See more at: http://consumercal.org/california-online-privacy-protection-act-caloppa/#sthash.0FdRbT51.dpuf

According to CalOPPA, we agree to the following:  
Users can visit our site anonymously.  
Once this privacy policy is created, we will add a link to it on our home page or as a minimum, on the first significant page after entering our website.  
Our Privacy Policy link includes the word ‘Privacy’ and can easily be found on the page specified above.

You will be notified of any Privacy Policy changes:  
• On our Privacy Policy Page  
Can change your personal information:  
• By emailing us

How does our site handle Do Not Track signals?  
We don’t honor Do Not Track signals and Do Not Track, plant cookies, or use advertising when a Do Not Track (DNT) browser mechanism is in place. We don’t honor them because:  
We need to track all visitors to provide visitors with the best possible experience.

Does our site allow third-party behavioral tracking?  
It’s also important to note that we allow third-party behavioral tracking

COPPA (Children Online Privacy Protection Act)

When it comes to the collection of personal information from children under the age of 13 years old, the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) puts parents in control. The Federal Trade Commission, United States’ consumer protection agency, enforces the COPPA Rule, which spells out what operators of websites and online services must do to protect children’s privacy and safety online.

We do not specifically market to children under the age of 13 years old.

Fair Information Practices

The Fair Information Practices Principles form the backbone of privacy law in the United States and the concepts they include have played a significant role in the development of data protection laws around the globe. Understanding the Fair Information Practice Principles and how they should be implemented is critical to comply with the various privacy laws that protect personal information.

In order to be in line with Fair Information Practices we will take the following responsive action, should a data breach occur:  
We will notify you via email  
• Within 7 business days

We also agree to the Individual Redress Principle which requires that individuals have the right to legally pursue enforceable rights against data collectors and processors who fail to adhere to the law. This principle requires not only that individuals have enforceable rights against data users, but also that individuals have recourse to courts or government agencies to investigate and/or prosecute non-compliance by data processors.

CAN SPAM Act

The CAN-SPAM Act is a law that sets the rules for commercial email, establishes requirements for commercial messages, gives recipients the right to have emails stopped from being sent to them, and spells out tough penalties for violations.

We collect your email address in order to:  
• Send information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions  
• Market to our mailing list or continue to send emails to our clients after the original transaction has occurred.

To be in accordance with CANSPAM, we agree to the following:  
• Not use false or misleading subjects or email addresses.  
• Identify the message as an advertisement in some reasonable way.  
• Include the physical address of our business or site headquarters.  
• Monitor third-party email marketing services for compliance, if one is used.  
• Honor opt-out/unsubscribe requests quickly.  
• Allow users to unsubscribe by using the link at the bottom of each email.

If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, you can email us at  
• Follow the instructions at the bottom of each email.  
and we will promptly remove you from ALL correspondence.
